(Sheldon:)Point of inquiry,
(Sheldon:)given that Leonard is
your secondary friend
(Sheldon:)and Koothrappali is
your primary friend,
(Sheldon:)why didn't you seek refuge
under his roof?
(Howard:)There's no room.
(Howard:)His sister is staying with him.
(Leonard:)Wait, wait. What?
(Sheldon:)Cocoa, Leonard.
Focus.
(Sheldon:)I'm down in
the dumps here.
(Leonard:)Priya's in town?
(Howard:)Yeah, some work thing.
(Howard:)Anyway, my mother seems
to think that Bernadette...
(Leonard:)Hold on.
When did Priya get here?
(Howard:)I don't know.
A couple of days ago.
(Howard:)The thing is, Bernadette doesn't
like that I have to take care
(Howard:)of my mother, and my mother
doesn't trust Bernadette...
(Leonard:)Yeah, that's a real pickle.
(Leonard:)Bye.
(Sheldon:)Don't worry.
(Sheldon:)As your tertiary friend,
(Sheldon:)I am prepared to step in
and comfort you.
(Howard:)That's not really necessary.
(Sheldon:)No, no. I'll finish
making the tea,
(Sheldon:)while you narcissistically
ramble on
(Sheldon:)about whatever's troubling you.
(Howard:)Thanks.